in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can use inkscape to draw objects
如何使用Inkscape绘制对象
that have a complicated Contour to them
它们有着复杂的轮廓
and a good example of this would be
一个很好的例子就是
these eyeglass frames which I've created
我制作的这些眼镜框
here for this demonstration so I'll be
在这里进行演示，所以我将
showing you how to create this before we
在我们为您演示如何创建它之前
get started though if you want to learn
不过，如果你想学习，就开始吧
more about how inkscape Works be sure to
有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息，请务必
check out my inkscape master class it's
看看我的Inkscape大师课
a collection of over 80 videos where I
收集了80多个视频，其中我
go over every tool and feature in this
查看此文档中的每个工具和功能
software and I explain what it is and
软件和我解释了它是什么，
demonstrate how it works we even have a
演示它是如何工作的，我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以在那里提问
questions and get help from me anytime
任何时候都可以向我提问并寻求帮助
you want so I'll have some information
你想要这样我会有一些信息
about that down below if you want to
如果你想的话请看下面的内容
check that out and with that out of the
检查这一点，并将其从
way let's get started so let me move
让我们开始吧，让我动起来
this out of the way and I'm going to get
别挡道，我要拿到
started by drawing a rectangle so I'm
从画一个矩形开始，所以我
going to grab my squares and rectangles
去拿我的正方形和长方形
tool and I'm going to draw a rectangle
工具，我要画一个矩形
and I'll grab my selection tool and I
我会拿起我的选择工具然后我
want to size this rectangle at 400x 200
要将此矩形的大小设置为400x 200
pixels so for the width I'll put in 400
像素，所以对于宽度，我将放入400
and then for the height I'll put in 200
然后对于高度，我会输入200
now we want to convert this to a path by
现在，我们希望通过以下方式将其转换为路径
going to path and selecting object to
转到路径并将对象选择到
path and I'm going to zoom in on this a
PATH，我要放大这张图
little bit now I'm going to grab my
现在我要拿起我的
nodes tool and I'm going to click and
Nodes工具，然后我将单击并
drag over these two nodes right here to
将鼠标拖到这两个节点上即可
select both of them and I want to enable
同时选中这两个选项，然后我要启用
this option up here in the toolbar that
工具栏上的这个选项
says show transformation handles for
表示显示以下对象的转换句柄
selected nodes I'm going to turn that on
选定的节点我要将其打开
and that's going to give us
这将给我们带来
transformation handles for these
这些对象的转换句柄
selected nodes and I'm going to hold
选定的节点和我要保留的
control and shift and I'm just going to
控制和移位，我只是要
scale these two nodes in about this far
将这两个节点扩展到这一步
now if you look at the bottom left of
现在如果你看一下左下角的
the screen it'll show you how much
屏幕上会显示你有多少钱
you're scaling it by for this
你为这件事把它放大了
demonstration I'm going to scale it by
演示我将按以下比例进行扩展
about 70% it doesn't have to be exact
大约70%的人不一定要准确
but somewhere thereabouts is good enough
但在那里附近的某个地方已经足够好了
and once you do that you can go ahead
一旦你做到这一点，你就可以继续前进
and disable this setting that we just
并禁用我们刚刚设置的
enabled and now that that's done I'm
启用了，现在完成了，我要
just going to click and drag this top
只需点击并拖动这个顶部
Edge right here to give this a nice
就在这里，让这件事变得更好
curved contour and I'll do the same
曲线轮廓，我也会做同样的事情
thing down here I'm going to click and
下面的东西，我要点击并
drag this down as well to give that a
把这个也拖下来，给它一个
rounded contour and maybe I'll bring
圆形的轮廓，也许我会带上
that up a little more and I'll do the
再往上一点，我就会做
same thing over here on the side edges
边上也是一样的东西
of the glass frame or the eyeglass
镜框或眼镜的
frame so now we're going to take these
所以现在我们要把这些
corners and make them rounded so I'm
并使它们变圆，这样我就
going to come up here to the toolbar and
我要到工具栏上来，
I'm going to select this option right
我要正确地选择这个选项
here that says add corner LP and once
这里说的是添加角点Lp和一次
you do that click and drag over all four
您可以在所有四个选项上单击并拖动
nodes right there and we're going to
节点就在那里，我们要
take this rounded node and bring that in
拿着这个圆形的节点，把那个放进去
and as you can see as I do that it's
正如你所见，正如我所做的，这是
rounding the corner of those nodes now
现在绕过这些节点的一角
right about there looks good once I do
就在那里，一旦我这样做了，看起来很好
that I'm going to click on just this
我要点击这一点
node right here and I'm going to make
节点就在这里，我要做一个
this one a little extra
这个稍微多了一点
rounded and that right there is about
四舍五入，就在那里，大约
the effect we're going for so I'm going
我们要达到的效果，所以我要去
to finalize this now by coming back up
现在通过回来敲定这一点
here to the toolbar and selecting this
此处指向工具栏并选择此选项
option that says object to path when you
选项，当您执行以下操作时，会显示对象到路径
hover your cursor over it click on that
将光标悬停在它上面，点击它
and now we've converted that to a path
现在我们已经把它转换成了一条路径
so let me grab my selection tool zoom
所以让我拿起我的选择工具缩放
out a bit and now I'm going to turn this
向外一点，现在我要把这个
from a solid object into a uh like an
从一个固体物体变成一个呃像
eyeglass frame so to do that I'm going
眼镜框，所以我要去
to first make this a lighter shade of
首先要让这个颜色变得更浅
gray and then I'm going to go to path
灰色，然后我要去PATH
and I will select linked path or linked
并且我将选择链接路径或链接
offset and that's going to create
偏移量，这将创建
another copy of it behind it so I want I
后面还有一份，所以我想要
want to make that other copy black so
我想把另一份做黑，所以
let me click on black and I'm going to
让我点击黑色，我要
take this node and bring this out about
把这个节点拿出来，让它
that far we want this Noe to be about
我们想要的是关于这一点的
that far and that right right about
那么远，右边大约
there looks good and I will click this
看起来很好，我会点击这个
button again that says object to path
再次显示对象到路径的按钮
now I'll grab my selection tool hold
现在我要拿起我的选择工具
shift and click on the gray object in
按住Shift键并单击中的灰色对象
the middle so that we have them both
中间的，所以我们两个都有
selected and we're going to subtract
被选中，我们将减去
them from each other by going to path
通过去PATH将它们彼此分开
and selecting difference and once you do
和选择不同，一旦你这样做了
that let's come over here to the fill
让我们在这里尽情享受吧
and stroke menu if you don't have your
和中风菜单如果你没有你的
fill and stroke menu open just come down
填充和描边菜单打开刚下来
here to the fill and just double click
在这里填充，然后只需双击
that and it should open over here on the
然后它应该在这里打开
right hand side and I want to take this
在右手边，我想要这个
and bring the opacity down roughly in
并将不透明度大致降低到
half and once that's done let's right
一半，一旦做完了，我们就对了
click on this and go to duplicate and
单击此选项并转到复制和
I'm going to hold control and bring this
我要控制住局面，把这个
object over here to the left like
对象在这里的左边，就像
that and I'm going to zoom in on this
然后我要把这个放大
right here and the reason why I made
就在这里，我之所以
them halfway transparent is because I
它们半透明是因为我
want to see where they line up I want to
想看看他们在哪里排队吗？我想
take this object and I'm holding control
拿着这个物体，我控制着
the whole time I do this to lock it onto
我一直这么做是为了把它锁上
the horizontal axis and I want to
水平轴和我想要
overlap overlap this object about that
重叠部分与该物体的部分重叠
far and you can see the area where they
在很远的地方，你可以看到他们
overlap right about there and I'm going
就在那里重叠，我要走了
to duplicate this object again I'm going
为了再次复制这个物体，我要
to right click it and go to duplicate
要右键单击它并转到复制
and I'm going to take this copy and put
我要把这份拷贝放在
it up here and I want to zoom in and I
它在这里，我想放大，然后我
want to make this object if I'm looking
我想制作这个物体，如果我想看的话
right about here I want it to intersect
就在这里，我想让它相交
with the other object right about there
另一个物体就在那里
and where I'm going with this is I'm
我要做的就是我要
going to create an object from this
要从该对象创建一个对象
empty space in here and I'm going to use
这里空荡荡的，我要用
that as sort of like the uh the edge of
这有点像，呃，边缘
the eyeglass frame there so once that's
眼镜框在那里，所以一旦它
done I'm going to position that right
完成后，我将把它放在正确的位置
about there you may want to try to
关于这一点，你可能想试着
visualize what this Contour looks like
想象一下这条等高线是什么样子
like going up top here so if you may
就像在上面，所以如果你可以的话
have to move it just to make it look
必须移动它才能让它看起来
more fluid I think right about there
更多的液体，我想就在那里
looks pretty good if it doesn't look
看起来很不错，如果不是看起来
perfect don't worry about it we're going
太好了，别担心，我们要走了
to address that in just a moment so let
来解决这个问题，所以让我们
me move this in just a little
我把这个移进去一点
more and once that's done I'm going to
更多，一旦做完，我会
select all of these so let me click and
选择所有这些，让我点击并
drag over all of them to select them and
将鼠标拖到所有这些图标上以选中它们，然后
now I'm going to go into my shape
现在我要塑造我的身材
Builder tool which is over here I'm
建筑工具，在这里，我是
going to click on that and I want to
我要点击它，我想
make sure I have the addition option
确保我有添加选项
enabled and then I'm going to click on
启用，然后我将点击
this object right here and then this
这个物体就在这里，然后是这个
object right here and it's going to make
物体就在这里，它将会使
them into separate objects and now I can
放到不同的物体中，现在我可以
go back to my selection tool and now I
回到我的选择工具，现在我
have that as a separate object and what
把它作为一个单独的对象和什么
I want to do now is take just this
我现在想做的就是拿着这个
object I'm going to make this red just
反对，我要把它改成红色
so I can differentiate it and hold
所以我可以区分它，然后拿着
control and shift and scale this up
控制和转换，并向上扩展
about that far we want this to be a
关于这一点，我们希望这是一个
little bit bigger and then I'm going to
再大一点，然后我就会
bring this in and place it right about
把这个拿进来，放在正确的位置
there now mine looks a little sloppy
现在我的看起来有点马虎
there's some Jagged edges in there don't
里面有一些锯齿状的边缘
worry about that we're going to smooth
担心这一点我们会平息
that out in just a minute the idea is we
再过一分钟，我们的想法就是
want to have this object that we can
我想拥有这个我们能做到的东西
work with and we can use as that shape
使用，我们可以将其用作该形状
for the edge of the eyeglass frame so
对于眼镜框的边缘，所以
let me move that out a little
让我把它移远一点
more and once that's done I'm going to
更多，一旦做完，我会
hold shift and click on the other
按住Shift键并单击另一个键
objects so we have them both selected
对象，因此我们将它们都选中
and I will go into the shape Builder
然后我将进入Shape Builder
tool again and I just want to click
工具，我只想点击
click and drag a line going through
单击并拖动一条穿过的线
those just to unify them all together
那些只是为了把它们统一在一起
and then go back to the selection tool
然后返回到选择工具
and now we have something like that
现在我们有了类似的东西
right there so now that that's set let's
就在那里，现在已经设置好了，让我们
go to our nodes tool and let's go in
转到我们的节点工具，让我们进入
here and clean this up so if you notice
把这里清理干净，如果你注意到的话
over here we have a bunch of nodes
在这里，我们有一堆节点
that's what's giving it that uneven look
这就是为什么它看起来不均衡的原因
I'm I'm going to take these three nodes
我，我要把这三个节点
over here to the left and I'm going to
在这里的左边，我要
press delete on the keyboard to get rid
按键盘上的Delete键可以删除
of them and you should be able to take
你应该能够把它们
this handle right here and just jiggle
这个手柄就在这里，摇动一下
it bit and you'll see it straightens out
它咬了一口，你会看到它变直了
so we have a nice straight fluid line
所以我们有一条很好的直线流体线
and then I'll take this handle over here
然后我把这个把手拿到这里来
and just straighten that out a little
把这一点理顺一点
bit we want a nice fluid curve going
我们想要一条流畅的曲线
through there and then I'm going to do
穿过那里，然后我要做的是
the same thing over here if you notice
同样的事情在这里如果你注意到的话
there's an extra node in here if there's
这里有一个额外的节点，如果有
any extra nodes get rid of them you only
如果有多余的节点，则只有您可以删除它们
want one node there and then I'm going
想要一个节点，然后我就走了
to take this handle and bring that out I
拿起这个把手，拿出那个，我
want to make this handle so that it's
想要做这个把手，这样它就会
going parallel with the other handle or
与另一个手柄平行或
the other side of the handle and once it
把手的另一边，一旦它
looks about parallel you can hold the
看起来是平行的，你可以拿着
control key and then click the node and
Ctrl键，然后单击该节点并
then it'll make it automatically smooth
然后它会自动使它变得平滑
and I'm going to take this and bring
我要拿着这个带着
that in a little bit so it gives it more
一点，所以它给了它更多
of a swoop and now I'm going to cut off
突然行动，现在我要切断
this little corner right here so let me
这个小角落就在这里，所以让我
grab my pen tool which is located over
抓住我的钢笔工具，它位于
here I'm going to click to add a point
在这里，我要点击添加一个要点
hold the control button bring the line
按住Ctrl键拉线
straight down click to add another point
垂直向下单击以添加另一个点
and then add some more points going
然后再加几分
around the outside and then connect it
绕到外面，然后把它连接起来
back to the starting point and I'm just
回到起点，我只是
going to bring this in a little
我要把这个带进一点
more right about there looks good and
更右边的地方看起来很好
then I'll hold shift and click on the
然后按住Shift键并单击
object so that we have them both
对象，这样我们就可以同时拥有它们
selected and once again we'll go to path
选择后，我们将再次转到Path
and select difference and now we have
并选择差异，现在我们有了
that little Notch there on the left hand
左手上的那个小缺口
side I'm going to shape this up a little
在这方面，我将对此进行一些调整
more let me go back to my nodes tool I'm
更多让我回到我的节点工具，我
going to grab this left Edge right here
就在这里抓住这个左边的边缘
and pull that out a little bit and I'm
把它拉出来一点，我就会
going to round these Corners just a tiny
绕过这些角落只有一小部分
bit so I'm going to come back up here to
所以我要回到这里来
the add Corners live path effect and I'm
添加拐角的活动路径效果和我
going to select just those two corners
只选择这两个角
and I'll grab this round knot right here
我会在这里抓住这个圆结
and just round those Corners a little
再绕过那些拐角一点
bit about that much looks good and then
差不多那么多看起来很好，然后
I will click this button over here that
我会点击这里的这个按钮，
says object to path and there we go I'm
对小路说反对，我们走吧，我是
going to select Ju Just this object
我要选择Ju就是这个对象
right here and I want to click on it
就在这里，我想点击它
again to get the rotation handles and I
再次获得旋转手柄和我
want to rotate this clockwise just a
我想把这个顺时针旋转一圈
couple of degrees just to give it a
几度，只是为了给它一个
little bit of a
有点像
tilt about that much looks good okay so
倾斜那么多看起来不错，好的，所以
now I'll uh duplicate it I'll right
现在我要，呃，复制它，我马上就来
click and go to duplicate
单击并转至复制
hold control bring this over to the
按住控制，把这个拿到
right and then I want to flip this
好的，然后我想把这个翻过来
horizontally to do that I'm just going
要做到这一点，我只需要
to press the letter H on my keyboard and
按下键盘上的字母H，然后
it's going to flip it horizontally and
它将水平翻转它，
then I'll just move this over a little
那我就把这个往前移一点
more just to space it out you want to
更多的只是为了隔开你想要的
eyeball about how far apart these uh
看看这些之间的距离有多远
lenses should
镜片应该是
be I think right about there looks good
我想对了吗？看起来不错
and then I'm going to draw a rectangle
然后我要画一个矩形
going
vbl.去，去
through the uh space between these two
通过这两个之间的呃空间
objects so let me grab my rectangle tool
对象，让我抓起我的矩形工具
and I'm going to click and drag to draw
我要点击并拖动来绘制
a rectangle going through there and I'm
一个长方形穿过那里，我是
going to grab my selection tool I want
去拿我想要的选择工具
to make sure that the bottom of the
以确保底部的
rectangle ends where this curve before
矩形在此曲线之前的位置结束
this curve begins over here so if it's
这条曲线从这里开始，所以如果它是
up here it's about too high because this
在这里它太高了，因为这
curve is already beginning I want to
曲线已经开始了，我想
bring it down here about that far where
把它带到这里大约那么远的地方
we still have a little bit of a straight
我们还是有一点直来直去
edge there and up here I want to bring
边缘那里和这里，我想带上
this up a little bit maybe about that
这个有点上升，也许是关于那个
far the placement up here isn't as
这里的位置远远不像
important as long as it's somewhere
重要的是只要它在某个地方
thereabouts it should be pretty good and
在那里附近应该很好，而且
now I will select everything here and go
现在我要把这里的所有东西都选好就走
into my shape Builder tool and I'm just
进入我的Shape Builder工具，我只是
going to draw a line going through all
我要划一条线，穿过所有
of these objects here to make them one
所有这些物品中的一件
single object go back to the selection
单个对象返回到选定内容
tool and now we're going to shape this
工具，现在我们要塑造这个
up so that it looks like this over here
向上，这样看起来就像这里
what it's supposed to look like so to do
它应该是什么样子才能这样做
that let me grab my nodes
让我抓住我的节点
tool I want to select these two nodes
工具我想选择这两个节点
right here and I want to add a new node
就在这里，我想添加一个新节点
in the middle so to do that I'm going to
在中间，所以为了做到这一点，我要
come over here to this button at the top
到这里来，到顶部的这个按钮
left corner that says insert new nodes
左上角显示插入新节点
and click on that and I'll take just
点击这一点，我就把它
that node I'm going to click on just
我要点击的那个节点
that node and hold control and bring
该节点并保持控制并带来
that down and I want to make this into a
我想把它变成一个
symmetrical node so I'll come back up
对称的节点，所以我会回来的
here to the toolbar and I want to select
在这里到工具栏，我想选择
this option that says make selected node
此选项显示为选中节点
symmetric and that's going to give us
对称的，这将给我们带来
this symmetrical node with these handles
此对称节点具有以下句柄
that move in and out uh the same way
以同样的方式进出
then I want to select this node over
然后我想选择这个节点
here hold shift select this node over
在此处按住Shift键选择此节点
here so that we have them both selected
这样我们就把它们都选好了
and I'll press delete on the keyboard to
我会按键盘上的Delete键来
get rid of those nodes and if you notice
去掉这些节点，如果你注意到
we're starting to get a little bit of a
我们开始有一点
we have a nice fluid dip in here so let
我们这里有很好的液体浸泡，所以让我们
me move this up a little more and I'm
我把这个再往上移一点，我就
going to move this handle out I'm going
我要把这个把手拿出来，我要
to hold control while I do this to keep
在我这样做的同时保持控制
it on its axis and I'll move this one
它在它的轴上，我会移动这个
out about the same
几乎是一样的
distance and then I want to take this
距离，然后我想带上这个
one and just bring that in a little bit
一只，只要把它带进一点
and if I go back to my selection tool
如果我回到我的选择工具
and click off of it you can see uh how
然后点击它，你可以看到，呃，是如何
it looks it looks pretty fluid but it
它看起来很流畅，但它
could look a little better so I'm going
可以看起来更好一点，所以我要去
to take this and bring that up a little
把这个和那个提起来一点
more that should help it look a little
更多，应该会让它看起来有点
more even okay that looks better and now
更好的，看起来更好，现在
I'm just going to use I'm going to use
我要用我要用的
the nodes tool again to take this bottom
再次使用结点工具获取此底部
Edge and just bring this up like that
边，就像这样把这个拿出来
and to straighten this out I'm going to
为了弄清楚这件事，我要
click on this node take this handle and
点击该节点，获取该句柄，然后
bring this straight up or not straight
把这件事直接提出来，还是不直
up but going up at the angle it want you
向上，但以它想要的角度向上
want it to match the angle of the edge
希望它与边缘的角度相匹配
of this Frame right here so I'll bring
就在这里，所以我会带上
that up about that far and then I want
大概那么远，然后我想
to take this node or this handle and do
获取此节点或此句柄并执行
the same thing we want to bring it up
同样的事情我们也想提出来
about just as high and again we want to
差不多一样高，我们想再来一次
use the same angle as the frame right
使用与边框右侧相同的角度
there and if I zoom out you can see we
在那里，如果我放大，你可以看到我们
are finished I can take the opacity and
都完成了，我可以把不透明和
bring it up to 100% And as you can see
将其提高到100%，如您所见
we have created those eyeglass frames
我们创造了这些眼镜镜框
with those really complicated Contours
用那些非常复杂的轮廓
using inkscape if you found this lesson
如果您发现这一课，请使用Inkscape
useful then consider checking out my
有用的，那么可以考虑查看我的
inkscape master class it's a collection
Inkscape大师类，它是一个集合
of over 60 videos where I go over all of
60多个视频中，我浏览了所有
the tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help for me anytime you want and
在你需要的时候随时帮我
best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会费你只需付17美元一张
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间和你在一起的生活我将拥有
some information about that down below
下面是关于这一点的一些信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地查看
thanks for watching
感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]
a
一个